So hey guys how are you all I hope
you all are fine so welcome back my
channel SAT 2.0 so friends you can see
here you can apply for ICICI card or credit
card here within a
few means by following simple steps that
too amazononline.in
[Sangeet] if
amazononline.in
city is not available then I will do it in other here
and write my city
name after that I will enter the PAN card number
now I will quickly fill up this form
friends you can see here I will
enter the name after that if you
work at gmailcom.in then you
can apply for salary so I will apply for salary and
enter the name of the company
ok
[Sangeet]
here I will enter the name of the company
after that here the account in which the money comes,
which no account salary account and here
you will click on saving current account because this is where the money comes in your savings account
then continue
after that enter the phone number here after that
OTP will come friends  Then you will enter the date of
birth here, which will be your correct
date of birth in Aadhar, you will enter it here,
after that click on the box here,
apply the terms and conditions, after that
submit it, friends, this is all you have to do, you do
n't have to do anything else, after entering the number here, you have to click on get
OTP, you can see here that the
OTP will go, you
can see enter here, the OTP has come,
friends, copy it
[music] and
paste it here, you
can see here that the OTP will enter,
friends, now what to do here, we will
enter the date of birth, it is ok
[music],
after that friends,
you have to tick the box here, you have to submit it here, you
can see here that it will be submitted,
your process will be
submitted and friends, within 24 to 48 hours
you will get notifications here
that your card here means that it has been
applied and here in
how many days will your card be made, what will happen
if your card is rejected due to any
reason, your civil score should be at least 700
plus  It should be so friends, if the civil score is
more than 700 then only you will be able to
apply for the credit card here, so if your
civil score is less than 700 then only
it will be rejected here, okay so
friends, now what to do here,
friends, the thing to do here is that
you have to go back here, then
within one to one and a half hours you will get a message here,
that too from IIC Bank, okay, that your
card has gone into processing,
if it is to be completed, it will
come to your address within one to one and a half weeks, friends,
your credit card will come here,
friends, so friends, in this way you can
apply for your IIC credit card here
amazononline.in
[Music]